http://www.cheatcodes.com/about/privacy/

GameCube
iPhone / iPad (iOS)
N-Gage
Nintendo64 (N64)
Nintendo DS
Nintendo 3DS
PlayStation / PSOne (PSX)
PlayStation Vita (PSV)
Xbox
Privacy Policy
CheatCodes.com knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By visiting CheatCodes.com or any other website owned by gamerID Network ("Network Sites"), you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy covers gamerID Network's treatment of personal information that gamerID Network gathers when you are on the Network Sites and when you use gamerID Network services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that gamerID Network does not own or control, or to individuals that gamerID Network does not employ or manage.
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, or fill out a form.
When registering on our site, we require select personal information (including your full name, city, state and email address). We also enable you to provide additional information, such as a bio, gamertags, online IDs, etc. In addition, you may choose to include a photo or avatar of yourself in your profile. You can control how your information is displayed and used by visiting your Account Settings page on gamerID.com.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
How do we use your information?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our Network Sites (we continually strive to improve our Network Sites' offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests). Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.
All supplied information is encrypted into our database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
Do we use cookies?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
No. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We reserve the right to release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for advertising, statistical, or other uses.
Opt-Out Policy
To opt out of receiving email communications from gamerID and/or Network Sites, please either click the Unsubscribe link included in the body of an email communication from us or visit http://gamerid.com/unsubscribe/.
Third party links
At our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our Network Sites. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account and going to the Account Settings page.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our Network Sites, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Terms of Use
Please also visit our Terms of Use, which outline your obligations and limit our liability when you're using the Network Sites.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on September 15, 2010.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us via email or by using the address and phone number below:
gamerID Network LLC
P.O. Box 848
Maple Valley, WA 98038
(646) 580-GAMER
Most Popular Guides on CheatCodes.com
Top 25 Hottest Video Game Girls of All Time
All Cheats to Spawn Vehicles in GTA 5
GTA 5 Full Vehicles List
Full list of GTA Online Missions, Payouts, and Rewards
Top 10 Best Grand Theft Auto 5 Cheats
Show CheatCodes.com some Love!
Tweet
Most Popular Games on CheatCodes.com
GTA V (X360)
GTA V (PS3)
GTA IV (X360)
NBA 2K14 (X1)
FIFA 14 (PS4)
Watch Dogs (PS4)
Call of Duty: Ghosts (PS4)
Titanfall (X1)
Assassin's Creed IV: Black Flag (PS4)
Battlefield 4 (PS4)
CheatCodes.com
Since 1996, CheatCodes.com has been the world's #1 source for game cheats, codes, guides, hints, news, and tips for Playstation 4 (PS4), Xbox One (X1), Wii U, PlayStation 3 (PS3), Xbox 360 (X360), Windows PC, iPhone, Android, Facebook games, and more. To find all the latest cheats, guides, hints and tips, visit CheatCodes.com first!
TOP GAMES
NBA 2K14 on PS4
NBA 2K14 on X1
FIFA 14 on PS4
Watch Dogs on PS4
Call of Duty: Ghosts on PS4
LEGO Marvel Super Heroes on PS4
Titanfall on X1
GTA 5 Full Vehicles List
Pokemon: LeafGreen Gameshark Codes (Pokemon LeafGreen - GBA)
CheatCodes.com's Top 10 Best Grand Theft Auto 5 Cheats
All Cheats to Spawn Vehicles in GTA 5 (Grand Theft Auto V - X360)
Submit
About
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Contact
Copyright © 1996-2020 GamerID Network LLC. All rights reserved. "CHEAT CODE®" and "Official Cheats Source™" are trademarks or registered trademarks of gamerID Network LLC in the United States and other countries and may not be used without permission. All other brands, logos, and/or product names are trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners.
